I am the third largest account in New Zealand after the bird Hector.
Wow!
You don't really understand social media.
We go through them!
-But ... -listen, I like you.
But your channel is a bit ... So, you need a little more ...
So, weave it in ... with a little LA!
A little music, young people.
It should be fun!
A naj's background.
You are absolutely right, Edwin!
And some iconic outfits.
Anyway ...
And grind on your message.
You talk about a hundred things at the same time.
You want more followers, huh?
Who is following you now?
Yes ... we will see ... Ulla-Britt in Växjö, librarian.
Look, she has fun pictures of her cat!
After all, one's followers tend to be as one's self.
When adults try to be "down with the kids" it can be Cringe.
Social media is about being able to reflect sig-
-and relate to the one who becomes the sender.
It becomes a bit of an age issue.
Speaking of it, I get spinning here.
Can we sit down somewhere else?
-We go out of here.
-Okay.
-I don't get him out of the channel.
-It does not matter.
Algorithms work a bit like a recipe.
If you think the information is the ingredients in a prescription-
-And then you will get a certain result.
A certain cake, if we are to take such a comparison.
In social media contexts you can say-
-Do the algorithms above all help to sort content-
-And determines what you as a user see first in your feed-
-or what kind of content you see more of.
It may be based on who you are and what you have liked and followed-
-But also what your friends have followed and commented, or where you live.
The important thing is that the algorithms are not created from nowhere.
It is not much.
We are elderly.
Instagram I run a lot, both for work and privately.
I have also started with Tiktok, work -related.
-What do you know?
-Facebook.
Basically.
Social media is fantastic, but there are some problems.
Yes, the younger generation is tired of everything being screamed out.
Now you want to be in private rooms and share things with each other.
You can say this, social media companies have built system-
-O which are created to target advertising as accurately as possible.
Yes Yes.
And we users, we are pretty much on our stuff.
We post pictures of what we are doing.
What has happened to you may have to do with purchased fake followers.
Purchased users?
I have to go and crisis!
It can be a bug.
Right?
Yes, like on Twitter when people were blocked because they used the word "Memphis"?
Accounts that used the word "Memphis" have been limited due to a bug.
It is something.
Hope it is.
-Can you make a summary piece?
-How are we going to do it?
We solve it.
Bot comes from the word robot.
It is a computer program to do automated data-
-Att from chatting in a customer service to spreading propaganda.
It depends on what it is programmed for.